Guide to the Harvey Williams Cushing Papers in the Yale University Library
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Papers held in Manuscripts and Archives, Part I
  - Special Files, 1886-1939; Series II; 43.75 linear feet (98 boxes, 49 reels)
    - Book dealer correspondence: Rappaport, C. E., 1925-1938 (Box 85, Folder 126, Reel 62)
    - Book dealer correspondence: Robinson, William H., 1931-1939 (Box 85, Folder 127, Reel 62)
    - Book dealer correspondence: Rosenbach Company, 1921-1935 (Box 85, Folder 128, Reel 62)
    - Book dealer correspondence: Rosenbach Company, 1936-1939 (Box 85, Folder 129, Reel 62)
    - Book dealer correspondence: Rosenthal, Erwin, 1929-1938 (Box 85, Folder 130, Reel 63)
    - Book dealer correspondence: Rosenthal, Heinrich, 1932-1936 August (Box 85, Folder 131, Reel 63)
    - Book dealer correspondence: Rosenthal, Heinrich, 1936 September-1939 (Box 85, Folder 132, Reel 63)
    - Book dealer correspondence: Sab-Sau, 1916-1939 (Box 86, Folder 133, Reel 63)
    - Book dealer correspondence: Sav-Schoen, 1921-1939 (Box 86, Folder 134, Reel 63)
    - Book dealer correspondence: Schoenh-Schu, 1915-1939 (Box 86, Folder 135, Reel 63)
    - Book dealer correspondence: Schw-Sow, 1919-1939 (Box 86, Folder 136, Reel 63)
    - Book dealer correspondence: Sp-Sta, 1919-1939 (Box 86, Folder 137, Reel 63)
    - Book dealer correspondence: Ste-Sy, 1919-1939 (Box 86, Folder 138, Reel 63)
    - Book dealer correspondence: Sawyer, Chas. J., 1915-1938 (Box 86, Folder 139, Reel 63)
    - Book dealer correspondence: Schuman's, 1936-1939 (Box 86, Folder 140, Reel 63)
    - Book dealer correspondence: Schwarz, Ignaz, 1934-1936 (Box 86, Folder 141, Reel 63)
    - Book dealer correspondence: Schwarz, Ignaz, 1937-1939 (Box 86, Folder 142, Reel 63)
    - Book dealer correspondence: Scribner, Charles, 1932-1939 (Box 86, Folder 143, Reel 63)
    - Book dealer correspondence: Sotheby and Co., 1920-1939 (Box 86, Folder 144, Reel 63)
    - Book dealer correspondence: Sotheran, Henry, 1920-1939 (Box 86, Folder 145, Reel 63)
    - Book dealer correspondence: Stechert and Co., 1919-1939 (Box 86, Folder 146, Reel 63)
    - Book dealer correspondence: Stevens and Brown, Ltd., 1915-1929 (Box 86, Folder 147, Reel 63)
    - Book dealer correspondence: Stevens and Brown, Ltd., 1930-1938 (Box 86, Folder 148, Reel 63)
    - Book dealer correspondence: Stonehill, C. A., 1935-1938 May (Box 87, Folder 149, Reel 64)
    - Book dealer correspondence: Stonehill, C. A., 1938 June-1939 (Box 87, Folder 150, Reel 64)
    - Book dealer correspondence: Sweet, Forest H., 1934-1938 (Box 87, Folder 151, Reel 64)
    - Book dealer correspondence: Ta-Ti, 1919-1939 (Box 87, Folder 152, Reel 64)
    - Book dealer correspondence: To-Tr, 1919-1939 (Box 87, Folder 153, Reel 64)
    - Book dealer correspondence: Tu-Ty, 1919-1939 (Box 87, Folder 154, Reel 64)
    - Book dealer correspondence: Taeuber and Weil, 1924-1928 (Box 87, Folder 155, Reel 64)
    - Book dealer correspondence: Taeuber and Weil, 1929-1933 (Box 87, Folder 156, Reel 64)
    - Book dealer correspondence: Taeuber and Weil, 1934-1936 (Box 87, Folder 157, Reel 64)
    - Book dealer correspondence: Taeuber and Weil, 1937-1939 (Box 87, Folder 158, Reel 64)
    - Book dealer correspondence: Tregaskis, James, 1919-1937 (Box 87, Folder 159, Reel 64)
    - Book dealer correspondence: U-V, 1919-1939 (Box 87, Folder 160, Reel 64)
    - Book dealer correspondence: Voynich, W. M., 1914-1926 (Box 87, Folder 161, Reel 64)
    - Book dealer correspondence: Voynich, W. M., 1927 (Box 87, Folder 162, Reel 64)
    - Book dealer correspondence: Voynich, W. M., 1928 (Box 87, Folder 163, Reel 64)
    - Book dealer correspondence: Voynich, W. M., 1929-1930 February (Box 87, Folder 164, Reel 64)
    - Book dealer correspondence: Voynich, W. M., 1930 March-1934 (Box 88, Folder 165, Reel 64)
    - Book dealer correspondence: Wa-Whe, 1919-1939 (Box 88, Folder 166, Reel 64)
    - Book dealer correspondence: Whi-Williams, 1919-1939 (Box 88, Folder 167, Reel 64)
    - Book dealer correspondence: Williams and-Wr, 1919-1939 (Box 88, Folder 168, Reel 64)
    - Book dealer correspondence: Weiss and Co., 1926-1936 (Box 88, Folder 169, Reel 65)
    - Book dealer correspondence: Y-Z, miscellaneous, 1919-1939 (Box 88, Folder 170, Reel 65)
    - Boston Society of Psychiatry and Neurology, 1923 (Box 88, Folder 171, Reel 65)
    - Bowlby tablet, 1930 (Box 88, Folder 172, Reel 65)
    - Brain tumor registry, 1932-1933 June (Box 88, Folder 173, Reel 65)
    - Brain tumor registry, 1933 July-1934 June (Box 88, Folder 174, Reel 65)
    - Brain tumor registry, 1934 July-December (Box 88, Folder 175, Reel 65)
    - Brain tumor registry, 1935 (Box 88, Folder 176, Reel 65)
    - Brain tumor registry, 1936-1939 (Box 88, Folder 177, Reel 65)
    - Brain tumor registry: negative microfilm, 1913 January-1914 Nov, 1922 April (Reel 89)
    - Brain tumor registry: negative microfilm, 1914 November-1916 November (Reel 90)
    - Brain tumor registry: negative microfilm, 1916 November-1921 April (Reel 91)
    - Brain tumor registry: negative microfilm, 1921 April-1922 July (Reel 92)
    - Brain tumor registry: negative microfilm, 1922 July-1924 January (Reel 93)
    - Brain tumor registry: negative microfilm, 1924 January-1925 May (Reel 94)
    - Brain tumor registry: negative microfilm, 1925 May-1926 June (Reel 95)
    - Brain tumor registry: negative microfilm, 1926 September-1927 May (Reel 96)
    - Brain tumor registry: negative microfilm, 1927 May-Oct, 1928 March-1931 August (Reel 97)
    - Brain tumor registry: negative microfilm, 1927 October-1928 July (Reel 98, Folder system_indicator_3f18f129a88c0cc3b1257a9e8e251ce0)
    - Brain tumor registry: negative microfilm, 1928 July-1929 January (Reel 99)
    - Brain tumor registry: negative microfilm, 1929 January-October (Reel 100)
    - Brain tumor registry: negative microfilm, 1929 October-1930 April (Reel 101)
    - Brain tumor registry: negative microfilm, 1930 April-December (Reel 102)
    - Brain tumor registry: negative microfilm, 1930 December-1931 Nov, 1927 June-August (Reel 103)
    - Brain tumor registry: negative microfilm, 1931 November-1932 October (Reel 104)
    - Brain tumor registry: negative microfilm, 1913-1936 (Reel 105)
    - Brain tumor registry: negative microfilm, 1914-1935 (Reel 106)
    - Brain tumor registry: negative microfilm, 1913-1936 (Reel 107)
    - British Base Hospital No. 22, 1915-1916 (Box 108, Folder 178, Reel 65)
    - Brookline property, 1916-1932 (Box 108, Folder 179, Reel 65)
    - Brookline property, 1936 February-May (Box 108, Folder 180, Reel 65)
    - Brookline property, 1936 June-December (Box 108, Folder 181, Reel 65)
    - Brookline property, 1937 (Box 108, Folder 182, Reel 65)
    - Brookline property, 1938 (Box 108, Folder 183, Reel 65)
    - Brookline property, 1939 (Box 108, Folder 184, Reel 65)
    - Brown (Horace Manchester) Library, 1934-1937 (Box 108, Folder 185, Reel 65)
    - Brunner thesis, undated (Box 108, Folder 186, Reel 65)
    - Cambridge University honorary degree, 1920 (Box 108, Folder 187, Reel 65)
    - Cameron Prize lecture, 1924-1928 (Box 108, Folder 188, Reel 65)
    - Canano, 1926, 1928, undated (Box 108, Folder 189, Reel 66)
    - Child neurology research, 1936-1937 (Box 108, Folder 190, Reel 66)
    - Cleveland, Boston, and Baltimore memorabilia, 1886-1887, 1891-1897, 1910, undated (Box 108, Folder 191, Reel 66)
    - Cleveland Medical Library Association talk: The Doctor and His Books, 1926 (Box 108, Folder 192, Reel 66)
    - Committee on Economic Security: correspondence, 1934 October-November 20 (Box 108, Folder 193, Reel 66)
    - Committee on Economic Security: correspondence, 1934 November 21-30 (Box 108, Folder 194, Reel 66)
    - Committee on Economic Security: correspondence, 1934 December (Box 108, Folder 195, Reel 66)
    - Committee on Economic Security: correspondence, 1935 January (Box 109, Folder 196, Reel 66)
    - Committee on Economic Security: correspondence, 1935 February (Box 109, Folder 197, Reel 66)
    - Committee on Economic Security: correspondence, 1935 March (Box 109, Folder 198, Reel 66)
    - Committee on Economic Security: correspondence, 1935 April (Box 109, Folder 199, Reel 66)
    - Committee on Economic Security: correspondence, 1935 May (Box 109, Folder 200, Reel 66)
    - Committee on Economic Security: correspondence, 1935 June-December (Box 109, Folder 201, Reel 66)
    - Committee on Economic Security: correspondence, 1936-1939 (Box 109, Folder 202, Reel 66)
    - Committee on Economic Security: documents, 1933-1935 January (Box 109, Folder 203, Reel 66)
    - Committee on Economic Security: documents, 1935 February (Box 109, Folder 204, Reel 66)
    - Committee on Economic Security: documents, 1935 May, undated (Box 109, Folder 205, Reel 66)
    - Committee on Economic Security: documents, undated (Box 109, Folder 206, Reel 67)
    - Committee on Economic Security: printed material, 1920-1934 June (Box 110, Folder 207, Reel 67)
    - Committee on Economic Security: printed material, 1934 August-October (Box 110, Folder 208, Reel 67)
    - Committee on Economic Security: printed material, 1934 November-December (Box 110, Folder 209, Reel 67)
    - Committee on Economic Security: printed material, 1935-1937 (Box 110, Folder 210, Reel 67)
    - Committee on Economic Security: printed material, 1938-1939, undated (Box 110, Folder 211, Reel 67)
    - Committee on Economic Security: printed material, undated (Box 110, Folder 212, Reel 67)
    - Committee on Economic Security: miscellanea, 1934-1935, undated (Box 110, Folder 213, Reel 67)
    - Consecratio Medici and other papers, comments on, 1928-1930 (Box 110, Folder 214, Reel 67)
    - Coolidge Hill Road, 1930,1932 (Box 110, Folder 215a, Reel 67)
    - Councilman, W. T., 1885-1933, undated (Box 110, Folder 215b, Reel 67)
    - Curricula vitae, undated (Box 110, Folder 216, Reel 67)
    - Cushing, Ezekiel Dodge papers, 1937 (Box 110, Folder 217, Reel 67)
    - Cushing, William Harvey Fellowship at Yale, 1925-1929 (Box 110, Folder 218, Reel 67)
    - Cushing genealogy, 1936-1939 (Box 110, Folder 219, Reel 67)
    - Cytology volume, 1926 (Box 110, Folder 220, Reel 67)
    - Diaries, 1893 (Box 110, Folder 221, Reel 67)
    - Diaries, 1929, 1930 Jul, 1931 (Box 111, Folder 222, Reel 68)
    - Diaries, 1933, 1934 (Box 111, Folder 223, Reel 68)
    - Diaries, 1936 (Box 111, Folder 224, Reel 68)
    - Diaries, 1938, 1939 (Box 111, Folder 225, Reel 68)
    - Diaries and scrapbooks
    - Diathermy
      See: Folders 229-234
    - Doctors in fiction, 1922-1930, undated (Box 111, Folder 226, Reel 68)
    - Dogs, 1921-1923 (Box 111, Folder 227, Reel 68)
    - Dr. Garth, the Kit-Kat Poet, 1906-1916, 1928, 1945, undated (Box 111, Folder 228, Reel 68)
    - Electro-surgery, 1926-1927 April (Box 111, Folder 229, Reel 68)
    - Electro-surgery, 1927 May-December (Box 111, Folder 230, Reel 68)
    - Electro-surgery, 1928 (Box 111, Folder 231, Reel 68)
    - Electro-surgery, 1929 (Box 111, Folder 232, Reel 68)
    - Electro-surgery, 1930-1931 June (Box 111, Folder 233, Reel 68)
    - Electro-surgery, 1931 July-1935 (Box 111, Folder 234, Reel 68)
    - Elizabethan Club, 1931-1937 (Box 112, Folder 235, Reel 68)
    - Elizabethan Club, 1938 January-June (Box 112, Folder 236, Reel 68)
    - Elizabethan Club, 1938 July-December (Box 112, Folder 237, Reel 68)
    - Elizabethan Club, 1939 (Box 112, Folder 238, Reel 69)
    - Emergency Committee in Aid of Displaced Foreign Physicians: A-F, 1933-1939 (Box 112, Folder 239, Reel 69)
    - Emergency Committee in Aid of Displaced Foreign Physicians: G-K, 1934-1939 (Box 112, Folder 240, Reel 69)
    - Emergency Committee in Aid of Displaced Foreign Physicians: L-O, 1934-1939 (Box 112, Folder 241, Reel 69)
    - Emergency Committee in Aid of Displaced Foreign Physicians: P-S, 1933-1939 (Box 112, Folder 242, Reel 69)
    - Emergency Committee in Aid of Displaced Foreign Physicians: V-W, 1919-1939 (Box 112, Folder 243, Reel 69)
    - Ercole Lelli and His Ecorche, 1932-1936 (Box 112, Folder 244, Reel 69)
    - Ether Day address, Massachusetts General Hospital, 1921-1922 (Box 112, Folder 245, Reel 69)
    - Financial records: check counterfoils, 1912 November- 1916 October (Box 113, Folder 246-251)
    - Financial records: check counterfoils, 1916 November- 1922 April (Box 114, Folder 252-257)
    - Financial records: check counterfoils, 1922 May- 1925 June (Box 115, Folder 258-263)
    - Financial records: check counterfoils, 1925 June- 1928 June (Box 116, Folder 264-269)
    - Financial records: check counterfoils, 1928 June- 1931 October (Box 117, Folder 270-274)
    - Financial records: check counterfoils, 1931 October- 1936 November (Box 118, Folder 275-278)
    - Financial records: check counterfoils, British, 1920 August- 1938 August (Box 118, Folder 279-282)
    - Financial records: general (yearly) expenses, 1922-1934 (Box 119, Folder 283)
    - Financial records: miscellaneous accounts, 1906-1939 (Box 119, Folder 284-285)
    - Financial records: miscellaneous correspondence, 1927-1935 (Box 119, Folder 286)
    - Financial records: household expenses, 1908 October-1913 December (Box 119, Folder 287)
    - Financial records: monthly expenses, 1916-1917 (Box 119, Folder 288)
    - Financial records: petty cash records, 1919-1939 (Box 119, Folder 289)
    - Flint dinner, 1921 (Box 120, Folder 290, Reel 69)
    - Food and Drug Administration correspondence, 1933 (Box 120, Folder 291, Reel 69)
    - Food and Drug Administration correspondence, 1934-1935 (Box 120, Folder 292, Reel 69)
    - Food and Drug Administration correspondence, 1936 (Box 120, Folder 293, Reel 69)
    - Food and Drug Administration correspondence, 1937-1938 (Box 120, Folder 294, Reel 69)
    - Fountain Club, St. Bartholomew's Hospital, 1939 (Box 120, Folder 295, Reel 69)
    - Foxglove material, 1927-1928 (Box 120, Folder 296, Reel 69)
    - Francis estate, 1923-1926 (Box 120, Folder 297, Reel 69)
    - Francis estate, 1927-1933 (Box 120, Folder 298, Reel 69)
    - From a Surgeon's Journal
    - Full time, 1915-1933 (Box 120, Folder 299, Reel 70)
    - Gastric ulcers, correspondence, 1928-1932 February (Box 120, Folder 300, Reel 70)
    - Gastric ulcers, correspondence, 1932 March (Box 120, Folder 301, Reel 70)
    - Gastric ulcers, correspondence, 1932 April (Box 120, Folder 302, Reel 70)
    - Gastric ulcers, correspondence, 1932 May-1938, undated (Box 120, Folder 303, Reel 70)
    - Gastric ulcers address, public response, 1931 March-April 13 (Box 121, Folder 304, Reel 70)
    - Gastric ulcers address, public response, 1931 April 14-Nov, undated (Box 121, Folder 305, Reel 70)
    - Glioma monograph, 1926 (Box 121, Folder 306, Reel 70)
    - Goetsch-Plummer controversy, 1920 (Box 121, Folder 307, Reel 70)
    - Graham, Dr. Douglas, 1920-1927 (Box 121, Folder 308, Reel 70)
    - Gray, Philip H. Fund, 1921-1924 (Box 121, Folder 309, Reel 70)
    - Gray, Philip H. Fund, 1925-1927 (Box 121, Folder 310, Reel 70)
    - Gray, Philip H. Fund, 1928-1930 (Box 121, Folder 311, Reel 70)
    - Gray, Philip H. Fund, 1931-1934 (Box 121, Folder 312, Reel 70)
    - Gunshot wounds to the head, 1918 (Box 121, Folder 313, Reel 70)
    - Gunshot wounds to the head, 1918 (Box 121, Folder 314, Reel 70)
    - Gunshot wounds to the head, 1918 (Box 121, Folder 315, Reel 70)
    - Gunshot wounds to the head: cases A-K, 1918 (Box 121, Folder 316, Reel 70)
    - Gunshot wounds to the head: cases L-W, 1918 (Box 121, Folder 317, Reel 71)
    - Gunshot wounds to the head: correspondence, 1918 February-October 9 (Box 122, Folder 318, Reel 71)
    - Gunshot wounds to the head: correspondence, 1918 October 10-1922, undated (Box 122, Folder 319, Reel 71)
    - Gunshot wounds to the head: photographs, undated (Box 122, Folder 320, Reel 71)
    - Gunshot wounds to the head: photographs, undated (Box 122, Folder 321, Reel 71)
    - Gunshot wounds to the head: photographs, undated (Box 122, Folder 322, Reel 71)
    - Gunshot wounds to the head: photographs, undated (Box 122, Folder 323, Reel 71)
    - Halsted, William Stewart, 1922,1927, 1930,1936 (Box 123, Folder 324, Reel 71)
    - Harvard Medical School
    - Harvard Medical School: administrative board dockets, 1916-1917 (Box 123, Folder 325, Reel 71)
    - Harvard Medical School: administrative board dockets, 1919-1921 (Box 123, Folder 326, Reel 71)
    - Harvard Medical School: administrative board dockets, 1922-1923 (Box 123, Folder 327, Reel 71)
    - Harvard Medical School: administrative board dockets, 1924 (Box 123, Folder 328, Reel 71)
    - Harvard Medical School: administrative board dockets, 1925 (Box 123, Folder 329, Reel 71)
    - Harvard Medical School: administrative board dockets, 1926 (Box 123, Folder 330, Reel 71)
    - Harvard Medical School: administrative board dockets, 1927 (Box 123, Folder 331, Reel 71)
    - Harvard Medical School: administrative board dockets, 1930
      See: Folders 364, 454
    - Harvard Medical School: administrative board dockets, 1931-1932 (Box 123, Folder 332, Reel 71)
    - Harvard Medical School: animal experimentation, 1908, 1913 (Box 123, Folder 333, Reel 71)
      See also: Folder 6
    - Harvard Medical School: animal experimentation, 1914 (Box 123, Folder 334, Reel 71)
    - Harvard Medical School: animal experimentation, 1915-1938 (Box 123, Folder 335, Reel 71)
      See also: Folders 7-9
    - Harvard Medical School Assistant residency: A, 1924-1925 (Box 123, Folder 336, Reel 71)
    - Harvard Medical School Assistant residency: Ba-Bl, 1921-1929 (Box 123, Folder 337, Reel 71)
    - Harvard Medical School Assistant residency: Bo-Bz, 1924-1931 (Box 123, Folder 338, Reel 72)
    - Harvard Medical School Assistant residency: C, 1919-1930 (Box 123, Folder 339, Reel 72)
    - Harvard Medical School Assistant residency: D, 1927-1930 (Box 123, Folder 340, Reel 72)
    - Harvard Medical School Assistant residency: E, 1923-1930 (Box 123, Folder 341, Reel 72)
    - Harvard Medical School Assistant residency: F, 1924-1928 (Box 124, Folder 342, Reel 72)
    - Harvard Medical School Assistant residency: G, 1924-1932 (Box 124, Folder 343, Reel 72)
    - Harvard Medical School Assistant residency: H, 1923-1931 (Box 124, Folder 344, Reel 72)
    - Harvard Medical School Assistant residency: J, 1925-1932 (Box 124, Folder 345, Reel 72)
    - Harvard Medical School Assistant residency: K, 1917-1931 (Box 124, Folder 346, Reel 72)
    - Harvard Medical School Assistant residency: L, 1919-1929 (Box 124, Folder 347, Reel 72)
    - Harvard Medical School Assistant residency: M, 1922-1931 (Box 124, Folder 348, Reel 72)
    - Harvard Medical School Assistant residency: N, 1930-1931 (Box 124, Folder 349, Reel 72)
    - Harvard Medical School Assistant residency: O, 1924-1929 (Box 124, Folder 350, Reel 72)
    - Harvard Medical School Assistant residency: Pa-Pi, 1923-1928 (Box 124, Folder 351, Reel 72)
    - Harvard Medical School Assistant residency: Pn-Pu, 1923-1928 (Box 124, Folder 352, Reel 72)
    - Harvard Medical School Assistant residency: Q, 1924 (Box 124, Folder 353, Reel 72)
    - Harvard Medical School Assistant residency: R, 1924-1929 (Box 124, Folder 354, Reel 72)
    - Harvard Medical School Assistant residency: Sa-Sm, 1921-1929 (Box 124, Folder 355, Reel 72)
    - Harvard Medical School Assistant residency: Sn-Sz, 1924-1926 (Box 124, Folder 356, Reel 72)
    - Harvard Medical School Assistant residency: T, 1915-1928 (Box 124, Folder 357, Reel 72)
    - Harvard Medical School Assistant residency: U, 1925 (Box 124, Folder 358, Reel 72)
    - Harvard Medical School Assistant residency: V, 1924 (Box 124, Folder 359, Reel 72)
    - Harvard Medical School Assistant residency: W, 1920-1931 (Box 124, Folder 360, Reel 72)
    - Harvard Medical School: Boston City Hospital, 1922-1932 (Box 124, Folder 361, Reel 72)
      See also: Folders 376, 377, 425
    - Harvard Medical School: Boston Lying-In Hospital, 1921-1922 (Box 124, Folder 362, Reel 72)
    - Harvard Medical School: Cabot (A. T.) Fellowship
      See: Folders 365-368, 375, 376, 432-448
    - Harvard Medical School: Children's Hospital, 1914-1930 (Box 125, Folder 363, Reel 73)
    - Harvard Medical School: Churchill appointment, 1930 March-April (Box 125, Folder 364, Reel 73)
    - Harvard Medical School: dean's office, 1914-1916 (Box 125, Folder 365, Reel 73)
    - Harvard Medical School: dean's office, 1917-1919 (Box 125, Folder 366, Reel 73)
    - Harvard Medical School: dean's office, 1920 (Box 125, Folder 367, Reel 73)
    - Harvard Medical School: dean's office, 1921-1922 (Box 125, Folder 368, Reel 73)
    - Harvard Medical School: dean's office, 1923 (Box 125, Folder 369, Reel 73)
    - Harvard Medical School: dean's office, 1924 (Box 125, Folder 370, Reel 73)
    - Harvard Medical School: dean's office, 1925 (Box 125, Folder 371, Reel 73)
    - Harvard Medical School: dean's office, 1926 (Box 125, Folder 372, Reel 73)
    - Harvard Medical School: dean's office, 1927 (Box 125, Folder 373, Reel 73)
    - Harvard Medical School: dean's office, 1928 (Box 125, Folder 374, Reel 73)
    - Harvard Medical School: dean's office, 1929 (Box 125, Folder 375, Reel 73)
    - Harvard Medical School: dean's office, 1930 (Box 125, Folder 376, Reel 73)
    - Harvard Medical School: dean's office, 1931 (Box 125, Folder 377, Reel 73)
    - Harvard Medical School: dean's office, 1932-1933 (Box 125, Folder 378, Reel 73)
    - Harvard Medical School: Dental School, 1924-1933 (Box 126, Folder 379, Reel 73)
    - Harvard Medical School: Dormitory Fund, 1923-1927 (Box 126, Folder 380, Reel 73)
    - Harvard Medical School: fellowships, 1914-1928 (Box 126, Folder 381, Reel 73)
    - Harvard Medical School: fellowships, 1929-1936 (Box 126, Folder 382, Reel 73)
    - Harvard Medical School: Graduate School
      See: Folders 423-424
    - Harvard Medical School: general correspondence, 1910-1916 (Box 126, Folder 383, Reel 74)
    - Harvard Medical School: general correspondence, 1917-1932 (Box 126, Folder 384, Reel 74)
    - Harvard Medical School: Harvard Endowment Fund, 1917-1921 (Box 126, Folder 385, Reel 74)
    - Harvard Medical School: Harvard Medical Society and Historical Club, 1914-1915 (Box 126, Folder 386, Reel 74)
    - Harvard Medical School: Harvard Medical Society and Historical Club, 1916 (Box 126, Folder 387, Reel 74)
      See also: Series I, Folder 1412
    - Harvard Medical School: Harvard Medical Society and Historical Club, 1917 (Box 126, Folder 388, Reel 74)
    - Harvard Medical School: Harvard Medical Society and Historical Club, 1919-1921 (Box 126, Folder 389, Reel 74)
      See also: Series I, Folders 1228, 1412
    - Harvard Medical School: Harvard Medical Society and Historical Club, 1922-1923 (Box 126, Folder 390, Reel 74)
    - Harvard Medical School: Harvard Medical Society and Historical Club, 1924 (Box 126, Folder 391, Reel 74)
    - Harvard Medical School: Harvard Medical Society and Historical Club, 1925-1926 (Box 127, Folder 392, Reel 74)
    - Harvard Medical School: Harvard Medical Society and Historical Club, 1927-1928 (Box 127, Folder 393, Reel 74)
    - Harvard Medical School: Harvard Medical Society and Historical Club, 1929 (Box 127, Folder 394, Reel 74)
    - Harvard Medical School: Harvard Medical Society and Historical Club, 1930 (Box 127, Folder 395, Reel 74)
    - Harvard Medical School: Harvard Medical Society and Historical Club, 1931 (Box 127, Folder 396, Reel 74)
      See also: Series I, Folders 846, 1228
    - Harvard Medical School: Harvard Medical Society and Historical Club, 1932-1933 (Box 127, Folder 397, Reel 74)
    - Harvard Medical School: lectures, demonstrations, and clinics, 1916-1920 (Box 127, Folder 398, Reel 74)
    - Harvard Medical School: lectures, demonstrations, and clinics, 1919 (Box 127, Folder 399, Reel 74)